http://www.benchmarkquality.com/hipaa-privacy-policy

Home
HIPAA Privacy Policy
HIPAA Privacy Policy
BENCHMARK NOTICE OF PRIVACY PRACTICESTHIS NOTICE DESCRIBES HOW MEDICAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU MAY BE USED AND DISCLOSED AND HOW YOU CAN GET ACCESS TO THIS INFORMATION.PLEASE REVIEW CAREFULLYWe are required by law to maintain the privacy of medical and health information about you (“Protected Health Information”) and to provide you with this Notice so you will understand how
we may use or share your medical and health information and our legal duties and privacy practices relative to this information. We are required to follow the terms of this notice currently in effect. We reserve the right to change our practices and
make the new provisions effective for all health information we maintain. If we make material changes, we will make the revised Notice available to you by posting it in a clear and prominent location.HIPAA Privacy Policy Document (PDF)
BENCHMARK NOTICE OF PRIVACY PRACTICESTHIS NOTICE DESCRIBES HOW MEDICAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU MAY BE USED AND DISCLOSED AND HOW YOU CAN GET ACCESS TO THIS INFORMATION.PLEASE REVIEW CAREFULLYWe are required by law to maintain the privacy of medical and health information about you (“Protected Health Information”) and to provide you with this Notice so you will understand how
we may use or share your medical and health information and our legal duties and privacy practices relative to this information. We are required to follow the terms of this notice currently in effect. We reserve the right to change our practices and
make the new provisions effective for all health information we maintain. If we make material changes, we will make the revised Notice available to you by posting it in a clear and prominent location.HIPAA Privacy Policy Document (PDF)
Our Story
Our Story
Newsroom
Living Experiences
Independent Living
Assisted Living
Memory Care
Skilled Nursing Care
